

PERSONAL DETAILS

• Ploossche Hof 42, Den Bosch, 5233 HB

06-42694688

wterterian@gmail.com

28 January 2005

TALEN

Dutch:

Native

English:

Near-native level

Armenian:

Basic

Russian:

Intermediate

William Terterian



PROFILE

ICT-student with an analytic approach and focus on practical solutions. Experienced in machine learning and software development, with in interest in technology and how it can be efficiently applied. Works in a structured and independent manner, but is also able to function well within a team.

https://portfolio-site-williams-projects-28d77663.vercel.app



SKILLS

- C#
- Python
- Java
- REST API
- React

- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- MSSQL
- Al, Machine Learning
- Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Teams



WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2024 - Present **Delivery Driver**, Sjoesie, Den Bosch

• Delivering meals to customers.

June 2022 - September 2023 **Factory Worker**, Omron

• Assembly work.

July 2021 - August 2021 **Warehouse Worker**, Omron

Order picking

November 2020 - February 2021 **Shelf Stocker**, A.S. Watson Group, Kruidvat

· Restocking shelfs.

December 2019 – May 2020 **Support (Internship)**, SWZ Care

 Assisting with cleaning, kitchen tasks, and engaging people in various activities.



EDUCATION

Fontys University of Applied Sciences, 01/2023 - Present

Avans University of Applied Sciences, 01/2022 - 01/2023

HAVO

Jeroen Bosch College, 01/2017 – 01/2022